https://www.motherwellfc.co.uk/privacy/

Matches
First team fixtures & resultsWomen fixtures & resultsLeague tables Next Fixture
Club
Advertising and sponsorshipLive streaming sponsorship packagesStadium advertisingProgramme advertisingPlayer sponsorshipMatch sponsorshipMatch ball sponsorshipPitch sponsorshipDressing room sponsorshipDigital media sponsorshipHire Fir ParkBirthdaysConferences & eventsWeddingsFunerals & remembranceFunction hire terms and conditionsEvents at Fir ParkCommunityAcademyAbout our academyRecruitment & scoutingThe Braidhurst campusAcademy policiesAcademy graduatesMedia relationsMatchday accreditationThe boardClub partnersHistoryHonoursRecordsThrough the yearsList of Motherwell FC’s Scotland internationalsPoliciesAnti-racism & discriminationDisabilityEqual opportunitiesNo smokingUnacceptable conductGround regulationsClub charterChild protection and safeguardingSupporter ServicesSeason ticket discount offersWell LotteryOur 50/50 drawDisabled supportersSupporters clubsBe a MascotJunior Steel ClubClub accountsContact us
Join the Well Society
We are owned by our fans. Join them today.
Feel the noise with our branded headphones
Get the ultimate Christmas gift for the 'Well fan in your life.
Tickets
2020/21 season ticketsFree kids season ticketsSeason ticket financeActivating your online ticket accountLink your family’s accountsMore ticket informationHospitalityBuy match ticketsFir Park entry pricesDiscount offersForthcoming matchesVisiting Fir Park Next Fixtures
Motherwell v St Mirren
Scottish Premiership, 12/12/20 15:00
Buy Tickets
Rangers v Motherwell
Scottish Premiership, 19/12/20 15:00
View all fixtures and results
Don't miss out while we're behind closed doors
Watch every home match live if you're in the UK and every Premiership game if you're abroad.
Store
Menu
The Well SocietyCommunityNewsTicketsFree kids season ticketsSeason ticket financeLink your family accountsActivate online accountVisiting Fir ParkMatchesFirst team fixturesWomen’s fixturesLeague tablesSquadsFirst TeamReservesOut on loanWomenTeam newsClubAdvertising and sponsorshipDigital media sponsorshipDressing room sponsorshipMatch ball sponsorshipMatch sponsorshipPitch sponsorshipPlayer sponsorshipProgramme advertisingHire Fir ParkBirthdaysConferences & eventsWeddingsFunerals & remembranceFunction hire T&CsSupporter ServicesDisabled supportersSupporters clubsOur 50/50 drawClub accountsAcademyAbout our academyRecruitment & scoutingThe Braidhurst campusAcademy policiesAcademy graduatesMedia relationsMatchday accreditationHistoryHonoursRecordsThrough the yearsList of Motherwell FC’s Scotland internationalsClub partnersPoliciesAnti-racism & discriminationDisabilityEqual opportunitiesNo smokingUnacceptable conductHospitalityShopContact the club
Motherwell FC on Social Media
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
YouTube
© 2020 Motherwell Football Club | Responsive Website Design, Development & Hosting by mtc.
Privacy
Privacy
Motherwell Football Club takes the privacy of all its customers and website users very seriously and takes great care with customer and user information.This privacy policy explains what information we will collect about you, how we will use it, and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure.By using this website you consent to us collecting and using personal information about you in accordance with the terms set out in this policy.What information do we collect?In order to provide you with our services, we may collect personal information about you from our website, telephone conversations, emails, and written and verbal communications. We may, for example, keep a record of your name, address, delivery address, email address, telephone number, date of birth and credit card details.We may also record details of any disability or health needs you may have at the time of booking an event or service which will take place at our premises to help to ensure your safety.How do we use your information?Any personal data relating to you will be used and recorded by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this privacy policy.We will primarily use your personal information to provide our services and products to you. We will also use the personal information that we hold to communicate with you, for example: in the event that the services or products you have requested are unavailable, for record keeping purposes, to recover debt and to help us to prevent fraud, to improve the quality of our service, for market research, or to track activity on our website.We may also create an individual profile for you so that we can inform you of services, products, events or special offers that may be of interest to you.In the event of the sale of the business or the integration of the business with another party we may disclose your details to advisers or prospective purchasers advisers.CookiesIn common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called ‘cookies’ on this site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.Our cookies enable us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our website.They also enable us to enhance your visitor experience by storing information about the products and services that you select between visits so that we can provide you with focused information each time you visit our website.Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent cookies being stored, however if you do turn cookies off this will limit the service that we are able to provide to you.Security InformationWe take the security of your personal information very seriously. When you submit your credit card details, we use industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to guard your information.In addition, we have security procedures in place to protect our customer database from loss and misuse, and only allow access to it when absolutely necessary, and then under strict guidelines as to what use may be made of the personal information contained within it.This website contains links to other websites. We are only responsible for the privacy practices on this site. We recommend that you check the privacy and security policies and procedures of each and every other website that you visit.What to do if you do not want to receive marketing informationYou have the right to prevent marketing information being sent direct to you. If you prefer not to receive information from us or from any other organisation to which we may disclose your personal information, you can opt out of further marketing by clicking the relevant boxes on the screen upon which you provide information or by writing to us by mail or email.Please note, however, that if you do opt out, we and/or they will be unable to keep you informed of new services, products, events or special offers that may interest you and our ability to inform you of ticketing opportunities may be affected.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change our security and privacy policies at any time. Accordingly we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review our current policies.
You might also like
Terms
News
Club Partners
Motherwell FC on Social Media
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
© Motherwell Football Club 2020. All rights reserved. Website Design, Development & Hosting by mtc.
